sarvsms.com 2013-10-10

# SarvSMS.com

### Privacy Policy 

As set forth in the General Business Conditions, SarvSMS provides services to persons who join SarvSMS as non-paying Members or paying Users ("Members" or "Users" or "you"). As part of the registration process for the Services, you are asked to provide certain personal information. The policy of SarvSMS is to protect the privacy of SarvSMS Members who are using any of the SarvSMS Services. 

SarvSMS may send Users periodic emails containing information about SarvSMS, administrative notices about a User's account (such as notices about pending activities), updates on new Service features, usage tips relating to the Services and user satisfaction questions. SarvSMS may also access user information for the following administrative purposes: 

(a) to examine system accounting logs and other company records to resolve email and other system errors or problems and 

(b) for billing purposes. 

SarvSMS provides you access to your Profile information for the purpose of reviewing and/or updating such information. In order to view or make any changes to your Profile, go to the SarvSMS home page, log into your SarvSMS address and click on SarvSMS Profile to update your directory information.

SarvSMS is concerned about protecting User Information and therefore we work to protect this information by utilizing all appropriate technology to prevent unauthorized access to the information you provide SarvSMS. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online. 

Since offerings and technologies change, we reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of our Privacy Policy or Conditions of Use at any time without prior notice. Please periodically review our Privacy Policy. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR REGULARLY REVIEWING THE SarvSMS WEBSITE TO OBTAIN TIMELY NOTICE OF SUCH MODIFICATIONS. YOU SHALL BE DEEMED TO HAVE ACCEPTED SUCH MODIFICATIONS BY CONTINUING TO USE THE SERVICES AFTER SUCH MODIFICATIONS HAVE BEEN POSTED OR INFORMATION REGARDING SUCH MODIFICATIONS HAS BEEN SENT TO YOU. If at any time you are uncomfortable with any change, amendment or modification to the Privacy Policy or Conditions of Use and wish to cancel your membership, please notify SarvSMS.
